# Michelle Sullivan

msul1031@gmail.com

(765) 400-9436

Racine, WI

LinkedIn

From the start of my career in pharmacy over a decade ago the landscape of healthcare and role of the pharmacy has changed dramatically. Many healthcare systems have seen the value of data driven solutions in improving patient outcomes and business practices. As a scientist at heart, my belief is that the accuracy and relevancy of that data should be paramount, especially when patient care decisions are involved. With my recent admin role, I was able to develop my skills and experience with data reporting and analysis and found a field that I would love to continue to grow in.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### IU Health - Quality and Compliance Specialist

November 2017 - November 2021

Indianapolis, IN

- Outpatient pharmacy admin role with various data analyst, visualization and reporting responsibilities
- Developed reporting and analysis process involving large amounts of data from a third party database for newly implemented opioid medication handling policy
- Assisted with implementation of new pricing structure for all retail locations by analyzing and correcting data
  pulled from our retail pharmacy system (QS1) to a third party vendor (Omnisys), utilizing the Omnisys tools to
  adjust pricing, then verifying that the changes had been implemented in our software (QS1) and manually
  adjusting as necessary
- Assisted in verification process when processing data conversions between retail pharmacy systems
- Weekly and on call IT helpdesk role for approximately 200 users of retail pharmacy system (QS1)
- Medical and pharmacy records retrieval, review and analysis for the purpose of reporting on insurance audits
- Reporting and analysis of medication incident data for the purpose of visualization and trend tracking to our local retail pharmacy medication safety group as well as the corporate system group
- Various reporting and analysis as requested by pharmacy staff, team members, system admin and corporate
  executives

#### IU Health - Riley Retail Pharmacy - Pharmacy Technician

April 2015 - November 2017

Indianapolis, IN

- Data entry and review of prescription orders with high speed and accuracy
- Implementation of CIM ordering system involving constant monitoring of the accuracy of inventory levels within the third party system and manual adjustment when necessary
- Reporting of medication incidents by entry into APMS web based platform
- Local troubleshooting of IT issues and escalation to system IT when necessary
- Accessing patient records and problem solving any issues related to prescription filling and patient care

### Wegmans Food Market - Pharmacy Technician

Jan 2009 - December 2014

Ithaca, NY

- Data entry and review of prescription orders with high speed and accuracy
- Member of team handling 800 1000 prescriptions daily
- Review patient records, process refills and trouble shoot any issues with patient care or experience
- In store trainer

#### **EDUCATION**

## **SUNY College at Brockport** - B.S., Chemistry

September 2003 - May 2007

Brockport, NY

Awards: Departmental Scholar

## **SKILLS**

Excel; Word/Adobe Acrobat PDF; Powerpoint; Google Sheets and Docs; Microsoft Teams, Onedrive, Sharepoint; PowerBI